question_data = {
    "response_code": 0,
    "results": [
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "General Knowledge",
            "question": "&quot;Ananas&quot; is mostly used as the word for Pineapple in other languages.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "General Knowledge",
            "question": "A pasodoble is a type of Italian pasta sauce.",
            "correct_answer": "False",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "True"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "General Knowledge",
            "question": "Jingle Bells was originally meant for Thanksgiving",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "General Knowledge",
            "question": "Dihydrogen Monoxide was banned due to health risks after being discovered in 1983 inside swimming pools and drinking water.",
            "correct_answer": "False",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "True"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "General Knowledge",
            "question": "Slovakia is a member of European Union-",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "General Knowledge",
            "question": "You can legally drink alcohol while driving in Mississippi.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "General Knowledge",
            "question": "Romanian belongs to the Romance language family, shared with French, Spanish, Portuguese and Italian. ",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "General Knowledge",
            "question": "Pluto is a planet.",
            "correct_answer": "False",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "True"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "General Knowledge",
            "question": "When you cry in space, your tears stick to your face.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "General Knowledge",
            "question": "&quot;27 Club&quot; is a term used to refer to a list of famous actors, musicians, and artists who died at the age of 27.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        }
    ]
}
